Guide to the Erroll Garner Archive, 1942-2010 AIS.2015.09 AIS.2015.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Memorabilia, 1946-2006; VII.
  - Jewelry, 10.
    - British Penny (3) (Box 62, Item 7)
    - British Churchill Commemorative Crown (1) (Box 62, Item 8)
    - Erroll Garner MGM Keychains (6) (Box 62, Item 9-11)
    - Pocket Watches (2) (Box 62, Item 12-13)
    - Earrings (3) (Box 62, Item 14-16)
    - Money Pins (2) (Box 62, Item 17-18)
    - Keys (7) (Box 62, Item 19-25)
    - Cigarette Lighters (4) (Box 62, Item 26-29)
    - Rings in Ring Boxes (9) (Box 62, Item 30-38)
    - Tie Bands (Box 63, Item 1-4)
    - Money Clips (Box 63, Item 5-8)
    - Cuff Links- Singles (Box 63, Item 9-11)
    - Cuff Links- Pairs (Box 63, Item 12-33)
    - Clinton/Gore Campaign Pin, 1992 (Box 63, Item 34)
    - Key to the City of Indianapolis (Box 63, Item 35)
    - Desk Supplies (Box 63, Item 36-37)
  - Oversized Material, 11.
    The Oversized subseries includes large promotional concert posters from Garner's performances, as well as Garner album covers, original artwork and some popular magazines.
    - Garner Cut-out (Oversize 64, Folder 1)
    - Garner Photograph at Piano (Oversize 64, Folder 2)
    - Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity Scholarship Benefit Town Hall Posters (3) (Oversize 64, Folder 3)
    - Up In Erroll's Room Posters (German) (Oversize 64, Folder 4)
    - Gemeni Album Cover (2), That's My Kick Album Cover (2) (Oversize 64, Folder 5)
    - Garner Concert Poster (5), July 1970 (Oversize 64, Folder 6)
    - Garner Songbook Covers (8) (Oversize 64, Folder 7)
    - Feeling is Believing Album Posters- Mercury Records (4) (Oversize 64, Folder 8)
    - Garner at Carnegie Hall Concert Posters- Red text (8), Yellow (2), Orange (1), White (1) (Oversize 64, Folder 9)
    - Garner at Carnegie Hall Concert Posters Green Text (11) (Oversize 64, Folder 10)
    - Large Concert Posters, folded (6) (Oversize 65, Folder 1-3)
    - Large Concert Poster Amsterdam, Space Held for Poster Undergoing Concervation, 1958 (Oversize 65, Folder 4)
    - Album Covers- Paris Impressions (2), Gemeni, One World Concert (Oversize 65, Folder 5)
    - Photograph, Other Voices album cover photocopy, newspaper clippings (Oversize 65, Folder 6)
    - Concert Posters- 8th annual jazz hall of fame concert, April 16-24 concert, Florida symphony orchestra concert, International Festival London concert (Oversize 65, Folder 7)
    - Charcoal sketch portrait of Garner (Oversize 65, Folder 8)
    - The Urbanite, June 1961 (Oversize 66, Folder 1)
    - Billboard Magazine, November 15, 1988 (Oversize 66, Folder 2)
    - Ebony, September 1946 (Oversize 66, Folder 3)
    - Evening Times Front Page (10) (Oversize 66, Folder 4)
    - Garner Campus Concert Posters (Oversize 66, Folder 5)
    - One World Concert Poster (Oversize 66, Folder 6)
    - A Tribute to Frank Schiffman (Oversize 66, Folder 7)
    - Garner Symphony Hall Concert Posters (Oversize 66, Folder 8)
    - A New Kind of Love Soundtrack Publicity (Oversize 66, Folder 9)
    - Souvenir Photos (Oversize 66, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1962 (Oversize 66, Folder 11)
    - Album Covers (Oversize 66, Folder 12)
    - Garner From Coast to Coast (44), 1958-1959 (Oversize 67, Folder 1)
    - Garner at the Maisonette Poster, Black Background (8) (Oversize 67, Folder 2)
    - Garner at the Maisonette Poster, Red Background (10) (Oversize 67, Folder 3)
    - Garner at the Maisonette Poster, Yellow Text (3) (Oversize 67, Folder 4)
    - Drawings by Garner (Oversize 67, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Articles (Oversize 67, Folder 6)
    - Gershwin and Kern Album Cover with designs (Oversize 67, Folder 7)
    - That's My Kick Album Cover with designs (Oversize 67, Folder 8)
    - Close Up in Swing Album Cover with designs (Oversize 67, Folder 9)
    - New Kind of Love Proofs (Oversize 67, Folder 10)
    - Erroll Garner A Night at the Movies (Oversize 67, Folder 11)
- Martha Glaser Papers, 1921-2010; VIII.
  Biography
  Pioneering Jazz music manager and civil rights advocate, Martha Glaser, was born February 15, 1921 in Duquesne, Pennsylvania, daughter of Samuel and Pearl Farkas, Hungarian immigrants, and sister to Bella Rosenberg. Martha Glaser (nee Farkas) attended Southwestern High School in Detroit and earned her Bachelor's degree in Government with three minors in Economics, Sociology and History from Wayne State University in Detroit in 1942.
  Ms. Glaser planned to pursue a career in public affairs and journalism, but following the Detroit riots of 1943 she became increasingly active in supporting human rights, taking a central role in the formation of the Entertainment Industry Emergency Committee to combat race hatred. Calling to "ensure the right of all people to live in our nation without discrimination," Ms. Glaser advocated, "a coordinated approach to unleash the optimum weight of the entertainment industry in the offensive against race hate."
  Ms. Glaser was the first Jewish American woman to be hired by the city of Chicago to work for the Human Rights commission to oppose discrimination. As part of that effort, she organized Jazz concerts working first with Norman Granz, promoter of "Jazz at the Philharmonic," (himself an advocate for the growing civil rights movement) and subsequently with agent/impresario Joe Glaser. She then went to work for the Disc Corporation of America as a publicist and organized the Jazz for justice tours throughout the late 1940's.
  In 1948 she created her own music management company and settled permanently in New York City, where the Jazz scene was in full flower on 52nd Street. It was in that milieu that Ms. Glaser met pianist Erroll Garner, and the course of her life was set. Mr. Garner, born in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, was a self-taught prodigy who astounded the music world with his seemingly limitless ability to improvise on the keyboard, despite a lack of any formal music training. While Garner was an artist, not a businessman, Ms. Glaser found that by combining her love for Jazz, her civil rights advocacy, and her innate business acumen, she was able, after signing an exclusive contract with Mr. Garner, to advance his career onto a level of prestige hitherto unavailable to Jazz artists.
  Garner's 1955 composition "Misty", quickly became a classic, and was the twelfth most played ASCAP song of the 20th Century, due in no small part to Ms. Glaser's untiring efforts to promote and maintain Mr. Garner's image as a world-class composer. Her success in that effort is evidenced in his long list of laurels, including a triumphant appearance at Carnegie Hall, winning the French Prix du Disque, and securing the only Jazz music booking contract with classical music agent Sol Hurok. Mr. Garner shared that roster with Andres Segovia, Isaac Stern, and the Bolshoi Ballet.
  Ms. Glaser's vision encompassed recording as well, and she was a pioneer in producing Mr. Garner's discs in the then-nascent Long-Playing format. In a singular instance, she instinctively secured a simple tape recording of one of Mr. Garner's trio shows, in Carmel California, and when it was released as "Concert by the Sea" on Columbia, it became one of the largest selling Jazz releases of all time.
  Throughout this unbroken record of success, Ms. Glaser never lost sight of her early devotion to equal rights; she inserted a clause into Mr. Garner's contracts prohibiting segregation of his audiences, a decade before the Civil Rights Act declared the practice illegal. Mr. Garner's worldwide fame notwithstanding, Ms. Glaser shunned publicity herself, although her record of success in the music business, which was dominated in the 1950's by males in executive positions, is testimony to her tenacious hold on a position of equality among her colleagues.
  Ms. Glaser was also a pioneer in the concept of musical artists owning the copyrights to their own work, an unusual concept at the time, and one of great benefit to Mr. Garner, who reciprocated with twenty seven years of loyalty to Ms. Glaser and their co-owned publishing and production company, Octave Music. After Mr. Garner's career was cut short by his untimely death in 1977, Ms. Glaser maintained her tireless effort to keep his music in its premiere position, securing hundreds of licensed usages and overseeing a continual stream of LP and CD releases drawn for her trove of studio productions of the pianist's work.
  Thanks to Ms. Glaser's diligence and perseverance and in keeping with her wishes, the full scope of Garner's recordings, including many newly discovered unreleased treasures as well as his first known recording in 1937 and his final concert, have been archived. These recordings, photographs, video, symphonic scores, memorabilia, legal and civil rights documentation span the tandem careers of two unique individuals, one an original jazz improviser, and the other a true innovator in the areas of human rights, the arts, and business.
  Ms. Glaser died on December 3, 2014 at the age of 93.
  The Martha Glaser series contains correspondence (personal and business), greetings cards that she received, calendars and daily notes of her activities, poetry and TV scripts created by her, financial documents, family and personal materials, educational records (primary, secondary, and college), race relations (during the 1940s in Chicago, Detroit, and the music industry), photographs, some jewelry, and legal papers.
  - Correspondence Outgoing, 1940-2008; 1.
    The Outgoing Correspondence subseries contains personal, legal, and business correspondence organized by date.
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1940s (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 49)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 50)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, 2004-2008 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Martha Glaser Outgoing Correspondence, Undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Martha Glaser Letterhead (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Incoming, 1940-2010; 2.
    The Incoming Correspondence subseries contains personal, legal, and business correspondence organized by date.
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1940s (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Martha Glaser Incoming Correspondence, 2005-2010 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Undated Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Undated Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Undated Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Greeting Cards, c. 1944-2005; 3.
    The Greeting Cards subseries contains personal and business correspondence organized by card genre.
    - Valentines Day, c. 1944-2000 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Easter/Passover, c. 1960-2003 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Halloween, c. 1980 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Hanukkah, c. 1960-2005 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Christmas, c. 1950-2005 (Box 70, Folder 5-14)
    - Birthday, c. 1960-2005 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Thank You, c. 1970-2000 (Box 70, Folder 16-18)
    - Get Well, c. 1980-2005 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - General, c. 1950-2005 (Box 70, Folder 20-23)
    - Post Cards, 1950-1999 (Box 70, Folder 24-26)
    - Letters, 1947-2001 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Photographs found w/ cards (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Stamps (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Envelopes (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Clients and Family Correspondence, 1952-2000; 4.
    The Clients and Family Correspondence series contains letters from Bella Rosenberg, Tiny Grimes, and Bill Farrell.
    - Bella Rosenberg (sister), 1960-1998 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Tiny Grimes, 1962-1964 (Box 71, Folder 2-4)
    - Bill Farrell, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Calendars, 1969-2002; 5.
    The Calendar subseries contains sparsely populated information about Glaser and are in chronological order.
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Martha Glaser Calendars, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Daily Notes, 1953-2000; 6.
    The Daily Notes subseries contains daily typed or handwritten sheets of paper that act as a diary recording the daily activaties of Glaser.
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1957 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 1990s (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, 2000s (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, Undated (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Martha Glaser Daily Notes, Undated (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Creative Writings, 1946-2001; 7.
    The Creative Writings subseries contains manuscripts, poems, short stories and TV ideas written by Glaser over the course of her long career.
    - It Happened on Wax Manuscript, 1948-1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - It Happened on Wax Manuscript, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Hot Rod Years Manuscript, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Hot Rod Years incomplete, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Hot Rod Years incomplete, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Hot Rod Years incomplete, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Hot Rod Years Complete, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Poems for Hot Rod Years, 1946-1948 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Songs for Hot Rod Years, 1946-1948 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Poems (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Poems (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Poems (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Daily Ideas, 1948-2001 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - TV Ideas, c.1953 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Radio Ideas, c. 1945 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Short Stories (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Short Stories (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Short Stories (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Erroll Garner Biography Notes, c. 1980-1990 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Inspirational Newspaper Clippings (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Financial, 1947-2008; 8.
    The Financial subseries contains royalty information, receipts, and statements relating to Erroll's music.
    - Royalty, 2001-2004 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Royalty, 2005-2006 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, 1955-2005 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Letters, 1957-2008 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Letters (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Financial Statements (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Financial Statements (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Tax Returns, 1947-1959 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Stock,1960 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Family and Personal, 1921-2000; 9.
    The Family and Personal subseries contains Farkas family correspondence, family history, reflections on Erroll, and personal writings.
    - Family History, 1843-1942 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Hungarian), 1939 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Farkas Family Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - CV, Resume, References, Grades, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Employment (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Martha and Dr. Robinson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Address Books (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Travel, 1957-1970 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Martha on Judaism, 1947-1960 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Martha on Judaism, 1947-1960 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Reflections on Erroll (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Gift List and Thank You Notes (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Personal Writings (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Jazz Articles (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1947 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Rhapsody in Black, 1935 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Art Work (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Publications (Also see o/s box #) (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Esquire's Jazz Book, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Martha's Articles, Notes, Clippings, etc., 1947, 1991, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Education, 1932-1941; 10.
    The Education subseries contains assignments, class notes, and other material from Glaser elementary, high school, and college years.
    - Elementary School and Memory Book (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Highschool Notes and Assignments, 1934-1938 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Highschool Valentines Day Cards (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Highschool Composition Books, 1934-1938 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Highschool Autographs (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Published Poetry (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Prospector, 1934-1938 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Prospector (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Prospector (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Prospector (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Wayne State University Blue Books, 1939-1941 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Wayne State University Blue Books, 1939-1941 (Box 77, Folder 12)